So on tools, we also again have deep research. So I don't want it to do deep research on this very topic because it doesn't matter that much anyway
You know, I don't want to have resources on where is the best coffee of Liam, you know
We also have creative image. Yeah, it's not for now. So I click send I click submit and afterwards
You'll see that Gemini will start answering me, right?
You
So it goes through Google Maps
You see Google Maps is also another powerful product of Google, you know, and these are all advantages
to Gemini being a product of Google and having all these
Companies and stuff, you know, and yep as you see, so it says that sounds like a wonderful way to enjoy your coffee
Leon has some fantastic spots and
Yes, as you see
It provides me with this so I can export this to sheets as you see so sheets is another product of Google as you see
These are all compatible with each other and it's so joyful when it comes to
Using Gemini, especially if you're a Google user if you're a strong Google user you'll enjoy it a lot, you know
as you see it says
Locations etc. It also provides us with Google Maps with those places and
Yep, that's all